ILR School Albany Extension Division Records /3071
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Albany Extension Division Records
1975-2007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/3071
1.5 cubic feet
1.5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Consists mostly of collective bargaining agreements, conference listings, and pamphlets.
7927580
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 30, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 20, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4062m: ILR School Extension Division Albany Office Correspondence /3059: ILR School Press Releases /3060: ILR School Foreign Visitor Information /3061: ILR School Reprints of Articles about the School /3062: ILR School Public Information Center Publications /3063: ILR School Industrial and Labor Relations (ILR) Forum /3065: ILR School Extension Division Records /3066: ILR School Alumni News /3069: ILR School School Scrapbook /3072 PUBS: ILR School Miscellaneous Publications of the School /3070 mf(d): ILR School Publication "For Our Information" (F.O.I.) Digital from Microfilm
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Albany Extension Divison.
7927580
- Guests - Entertained by Capital District Office, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- New Office Space, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Office Space, 1951-1955 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- West German Industrial Relations Trainees Visit to C BA 2/2-2/4/53, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Conferences and Institutes offered by N.Y.S.S.I.L.R. on campus at Ithaca, New York, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Bigelow Institute of Industrial Management, 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Conferences and Institutes offered by N.Y.S.S.I.L.R. on campus at Ithaca, New York, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Conferences and Institutes offered by N.Y.S.S.I.L.R. on campus, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Conferences and Institutes offered by N.Y.S.S.I.L.R. on campus at Ithaca, New York, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Conferences and Institutes offered by N.Y.S.S.I.L.R. on campus at Ithaca, New York, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Journey to Work Project, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Attitude Survey - F.C. Huyck Son Confidential, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Agreements AFSCME, 1985-2003 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Agreements CSEA, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Agreements CSEA, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Agreements CSEA, 2003-2007 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Agreements National Treasury Employees Union, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Agreements NYSCOPBA, 2003-2007 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Agreements Public Employees Federation, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Agreements Public Employees Federation, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Agreements Public Employees Federation, 1999-2007 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Agreements SEIU, Local 200-D, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Agreements Teamsters, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Agreements UAW, 1976-1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Agreements United Steelworkers of America, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Constitution AFL-CIO, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Constitutions United Steel workers of America, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Pamphlets Institute for Women and Work (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Pamphlets our State Safety and Health Laws. Lois S. Gray, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Pamphlets A. Political Action Handbook CSEA (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Pamphlets. Steward Manual CSEA, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Pamphlets The Working Mother Alice H. Cook, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Social Behavior and Work Anne. H. Nelson, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)